const data = {
    api: {
        "id":78,
        "title":"world capitals",
        "clues_count":140,
        "clues": [
            {
                "id": 481, "answer": "San Jose", "question": "Costa Rican capital people might know the way to", "value": 100, "airdate": "1984-09-25T12:00:00.000Z", "category_id": 78, "game_id": null, "invalid_count": null
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id": 487, "answer": "Tokyo", "question": "It's divided into the Kanda, Marunoucki, Asakusa \u0026 Ginza districts", "value": 200, "airdate": "1984-09-25T12:00:00.000Z", "category_id": 78, "game_id": null, "invalid_count": null
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id": 493, "answer": "Brussels", "question": "Home to NATO \u0026 little green sprouts", "value": 300, "airdate": "1984-09-25T12:00:00.000Z", "category_id": 78, "game_id": null, "invalid_count": null
                },
                {
                    "id": 481, "answer": "San Jose", "question": "Costa Rican capital people might know the way to", "value": 100, "airdate": "1984-09-25T12:00:00.000Z", "category_id": 78, "game_id": null, "invalid_count": null
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id": 487, "answer": "Tokyo", "question": "It's divided into the Kanda, Marunoucki, Asakusa \u0026 Ginza districts", "value": 200, "airdate": "1984-09-25T12:00:00.000Z", "category_id": 78, "game_id": null, "invalid_count": null
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id": 493, "answer": "Brussels", "question": "Home to NATO \u0026 little green sprouts", "value": 300, "airdate": "1984-09-25T12:00:00.000Z", "category_id": 78, "game_id": null, "invalid_count": null
                },
                {
                    "id": 481, "answer": "San Jose", "question": "Costa Rican capital people might know the way to", "value": 100, "airdate": "1984-09-25T12:00:00.000Z", "category_id": 78, "game_id": null, "invalid_count": null
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id": 487, "answer": "Tokyo", "question": "It's divided into the Kanda, Marunoucki, Asakusa \u0026 Ginza districts", "value": 200, "airdate": "1984-09-25T12:00:00.000Z", "category_id": 78, "game_id": null, "invalid_count": null
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id": 493, "answer": "Brussels", "question": "Home to NATO \u0026 little green sprouts", "value": 300, "airdate": "1984-09-25T12:00:00.000Z", "category_id": 78, "game_id": null, "invalid_count": null
                },
                {
                    "id": 481, "answer": "San Jose", "question": "Costa Rican capital people might know the way to", "value": 100, "airdate": "1984-09-25T12:00:00.000Z", "category_id": 78, "game_id": null, "invalid_count": null
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id": 487, "answer": "Tokyo", "question": "It's divided into the Kanda, Marunoucki, Asakusa \u0026 Ginza districts", "value": 200, "airdate": "1984-09-25T12:00:00.000Z", "category_id": 78, "game_id": null, "invalid_count": null
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id": 493, "answer": "Brussels", "question": "Home to NATO \u0026 little green sprouts", "value": 300, "airdate": "1984-09-25T12:00:00.000Z", "category_id": 78, "game_id": null, "invalid_count": null
                }
        ]
    },
    header: {
        title: 'Quizzzy'
    },
    footer: {
        author: 'Hetic W2',
        service: {
            by: 'Powered by',
            name: 'jService',
        }
    },
    error: {
        title: 'Oops !',
        disclaimer: 'It appears that resources couldn\'t be loaded properly, please :',
        instructions: [
            `1. Click on the shield on the right of your adress bar`,
            `2. Click on "Load Unsafe Scripts" to load the content`
        ],
        cta: 'Try again'
    },
    categories: [
        {
            name: 'DEFAULT_CATEGORY',
            url: 'http://jservice.io/api/category?id=78',
            index: 0
        },
        {
            name: 'DEFAULT_CATEGORY',
            url: 'http://jservice.io/api/category?id=2537',
            index: 1
        },
        {
            name: 'DEFAULT_CATEGORY',
            url: 'http://jservice.io/api/category?id=2289',
            index: 2
        }
    ],
    category: {
        title: {
            welcome: 'Welcome on',
            name: 'Quizzzy'
        },
        desc: 'Click on the tile to begin'
    },
    result: {
        win: 'Your\'re a winner !',
        mid: 'You can do better !',
        loose: 'You lost !',
        another: 'Come on !',
        again: 'Let\'s see how good you are !'
    }
}

export default data;